GINA B. FLAGG

61 Imlay Street (860) 519-5853 Hartford, CT 06105 gbf77@hotmail.com

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Experienced professional with a successful track record in Administrative Support, Customer Service and Marketing. A proactive and versatile problem solver who implements solutions efficiently and effectively. Recognized for superior customer service, interpersonal, organizational and communication skills. Meticulous attention to detail; and the ability to prioritize and produce under pressure with exceptional results.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GORDON, MUIR & FOLEY LLP - Hartford, Connecticut

2005 - 2009

Legal Secretary - Construction & Insurance Defense

Provided full administrative support for three attorneys (construction, insurance defense, workers' compensation, bankruptcy, tax law). Drafted and prepared correspondence and legal pleadings (transcription included). Prepared and filed court documents with state, federal, and bankruptcy courts; and workers' compensation commission (includes e-filing). Had daily contact with courts, clients, and other counsel. Opened new files and maintained filing system. Entered and coded file data in Summation database.

Green & Levine, LLP – Farmington, Connecticut

2002 - 2005

Paralegal - Commercial & Residential Real Estate

Sole paralegal responsible for all residential real estate closings. Performed title searches and rundowns for residential closings. Entered time entries and maintained billing system; including issuance of invoices and process of payments. Drafted correspondence, lease abstracts, and lease summaries. Handled administrative duties, ranging from drafting correspondence to ordering supplies. Maintained working relationship with vendors. Opened new files and maintained the filing system.

Cable Rep Advertising – Newport News, Virginia

2000 - 2001

Administrative Sales Assistant

Drafted and sent correspondence to clients; acted as liaison between clients and account executives. Monitored clients' ads. Assisted the sales manager and account executive by performing administrative duties (proposals, ratings, schedules, etc.). Performed routine sales maintenance and sales staff support (weekly/monthly sales audits). Assisted in coordination of Co-op Advertising invoicing.

THE VIRGINIAN PILOT – Norfolk, VA

1999

Human Resources Assistant

Responded to phone and in-person requests for employment related information and assistance. Coordinated drug screenings, job postings, employee record keeping; and maintained jobs line. Created new employee orientation packets. Assisted in coordination of employee events and programs hosted by HR.

PolyGram Entertainment – New York, New York

1997 - 1998

College Film Representative

Developed and implemented marketing strategies to promote PolyGram films to major college campuses in the Virginia market. Increased visibility by creating displays and setting up promotions with student organizations and local businesses. Attended sneak previews to report attendance and audience reaction.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, Outlook, Internet; Abacus Law, Admall, AdTelligence, Aldus PageMaker, CableScanV2, CATIC HUDPrep, CATIC Polprep, Fidelity National Title Policy Maker, Fidelty National Title HUD Program, Lotus Notes, Photoshop, Qualitap, Quickbooks, SalesScan, Summation, Timeslips Billing System, Westlaw

EDUCATION AND PROFESSIONAL ASSOCIATIONS

B.S. Marketing – Hampton University, Hampton, VA – May 2000

Professional Paralegal Certificate - St. Joseph's College for Women, West Hartford, CT - Spring 2005

CATIC – Real Property Pursuit: Basic Closing Procedures, Rocky Hill, CT – Summer 2002

Notary Public

REFERENCES

Available upon request.